http://www.angliac.com/privacy.asp

We use cookies to ensure that we can provide you with the best experience on our website. By using our website, you are consenting to the use of cookies as set out in our policy. More Info
Anglia Components
Please login
Supplier sections
Aavid Thermalloy
ABL Aluminium Components
Advantech
Analog Devices
Antenova
Hirose introduce the DF61 series Wire to Board Connector for Power Supplies, samples available from Anglia
Click Here
Rate this page
You
can now follow us on Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter or You Tube by clicking on
the logos below.
Anglia delivers by
Recognised as the UK’s number one for reliability, flexibility and customer service.
Anglia Online Privacy Statement
About Us
This is
a privacy policy for Anglia Components Ltd. Our homepage on the Web is located
at http://www.anglia.com. The full text of
our privacy policy is available on the Web at http://www.anglia.com/privacy.asp.
Anglia provides this Online Privacy Statement to make you aware of our privacy
policy.
What this
Privacy Policy Covers
This Privacy Policy
covers Anglia's treatment of personally identifiable information that Anglia
collects when you are on the Anglia website, www.anglia.com.
We
recognise your need for reasonable control of "personally identifiable"
information that you share with Anglia via our website.
"Personally identifiable"
information is any information that is associated with your name.
Anglia
may use this information to improve your experience on our website by providing
personalised content based on preferences you send us via the internet so, for
example, we can provide new product information only for products you are
interested in.
Our
policy regarding the privacy of your information covers the following
areas:
Information Collected by Anglia
In order
to access certain portions of our websites, users must register and provide
certain voluntary information about themselves.
Anglia collects
personally identifiable information when you register with anglia.com, when you
request certain Anglia products or services and when you visit www.anglia.com
pages.
When you register
with anglia.com, we ask for your name, telephone and fax information, email
address, the name of the company you work for and its business address, as well
as your personal interests in areas of electronic components. Once you register
with www.anglia.com, you are not anonymous to us.
Anglia also
automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your
browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you
requested.
P3P
policies declare the data they collect in groups (also referred to as
"statements"). This policy contains 2 data groups. The data practices of each
group will be explained seperately.
Group "Basic information"
We
collect the following information:
data will be used for the following purposes:
Completion and
support of the current activity.
Web site and
system administration.
Research and
development.
Tailoring.
User
analysis.
User profiling and
decision-making.
Data is collected
from all Web users: access logs and search strings (if entered).
Group
"Cookies"
Anglia may set and
access cookies on your computer. Cookies are a technology which can be used to
provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of
data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your
system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving
you the chance to decide whether to accept it.
Our site makes use of cookies.
Cookies are used for user targeting, user analysis, research and
development.
We collect the
following information:
used for the following purposes:
Research and
development.
Tailoring.
User
analysis.
User profiling and
decision-making.
Use of
Information
Anglia
uses personally identifiable information for three general purposes: to
customise the content you see, based on the details given by you at
registration, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to
contact you about and new products we believe you will be interested in.
Anglia
uses users IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to
administer our website.
Using
e-mail addresses provided at registration or otherwise, Anglia may periodically
send out promotional e-mail to our users about services and products offered by
Anglia. Users can indicate that they do not wish to receive further e-mail
information from Anglia. Upon request, Anglia will remove users (and their
information) from our database or permit them to "opt-out" of any further e-mail
newsletters or contact by visiting http://www.anglia.com/registration/userinfo/userupdate.asp
Information
Sharing and Disclosure
Anglia will not
sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.
Your Ability
to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences
Anglia gives you
the ability to edit your www.anglia.com account information and preferences at
any time, including whether you want Anglia to contact you about new products.
Upon request, Anglia will remove users (and their information) from our database
or permit them to "opt-out" of any further e-mail newsletters or contact by
visiting http://www.anglia.com/registration/userinfo/userupdate.asp
Security
Anglia is committed
to ensuring the security of your information and uses reasonable precautions to
keep the personal information disclosed to us secure. Your Account Information
is password-protected for your privacy and security. Anglia will not reveal any
personal information that users provide to us to any third party without their
permission.
Changes to
this Privacy Policy
Anglia may amend
this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we
use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent
announcement on our pages.
Dispute Resolution and Privacy Seals
We have
no privacy seals or other assurance mechanisms.
Additional Information
This
policy is valid for 1 week from the time that it is loaded by a client.
Questions or
Suggestions
We invite you to
contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by mail
at the following address:
Anglia
Sandall Road
Wisbech, Cambs PE13 2PS
England
You may contact us by e-mail at privacy@anglia.com. You may call us at
01945 474747.
This
statement should be read in conjunction with our terms and
conditions statement.
Anglia Sitemap
Home
About
Company Overview
Why Do Customers Choose Anglia?
Copyright © 1995-2020 Anglia Components Ltd.
Please read our Privacy & Cookie Policy in conjunction with the Terms and Conditions and Terms of Use of this Website.
25/05/11
